Russell Trzaska

Full Stack Web Developer

trzruss@me.com

609-217-2562

https://www.linkedin.com/in/russelltrzaska/ https://www.russtrz.com https://github.com/helloWerld

I am a Full Stack Web Developer recently completing Nucamp's Full Stack Web and Mobile Development Bootcamp. I have I year of professional experience developing SEO friendly websites using HTML, CSS, and Wordpress. I'm passionate about React.js, Front-end, and Web3 technologies, and seek a web developer position to apply my skills and continue learning in a team environment.

PROJECTS (more available on Github)

Click Promote (MERN Stack) - An Online Marketplace For Influencers & Advertisers A two-sided marketplace that connects content creators with businesses who need promotion.

Simple Weather (HTML, CSS, JS) - A Simple Weather Forecast Chrome Extension

Chrome extension that pulls current and future weather conditions from the WeatherAPI.com REST API.

YouTube Viral Finder (Python) - A Python Script To Find Viral YouTube Videos
Command line script to search the YouTube Data API for viral videos based on a keyword search.

SKILLS

Advanced: React, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Python, Bootstrap, REST APIs

Familiar: SQL, React Native, Node, Express, MondoDB, Git, Docker, Django, AWS Cloud

No-code: Wordpress, Photoshop, Figma, InDesign

EDUCATION

Ethereum Developer Bootcamp - Alchemy University, Online | Dec 2022 - Present
Full Stack Software Engineering Bootcamp - Nucamp, Online | Mar 2022 - Dec 2022
Bachelor of Science, Plant Science - Rutgers University, New Jersey | Sep 2007 - Jun 2011

EXPERIENCE

Shore Building Contractors, Inc. - Freelance Web Developer

Remote | Oct 2022 - Dec 2022

Designed, developed, and deployed a new company website based on owner's specifications.

BigWeek Marketing - SEO Consultant

Philadelphia, PA | Mar 2016 - Apr 2017

Utilized HTML, CSS, and Javascript to develop, maintain, and optimize client websites for organic search rankings, using SEO best practices.